Guide to the Mark D. Weiser Papers, 1969-1999
Department of Special Collections
- Series 5. Subject files
  - Merrill Lynch - economic "passages" (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Microsoft (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Microsoft Windows NT source code agreement (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - MIT (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - MIT Media Laboratory (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - MIT Media Laboratory - Digital Life Consortium (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - MIT Media Laboratory, 1997 Jan. 10 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - MIT Media Laboratory, 1997 Mar. 10 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - MIT Media Laboratory - patent application "Hetergeneous display elements & methods for their fabrication" (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - MIT Media Laboratory - patent application (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - MIT X Consortium (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - MMM [Monthly Management Meeting] binder [1 of 3], 1997 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - MMM [Monthly Management Meeting] binder [2 of 3], 1997 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - MMM [Monthly Management Meeting] binder [3 of 3], 1997 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - MMM [Monthly Management Meeting] binder [1 of 3], 1998 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - MMM [Monthly Management Meeting] binder [2 of 3], 1998 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - MMM [Monthly Management Meeting] binder [3 of 3], 1998 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Mobile, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Mobile computing (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Mobile Computing Application Consortium (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Mobile data market segment (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Momentum Micro: miscellaneous writings (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Momentum Micro: Momentum Wireless (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Motorola (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Motorola, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Mudge, Craig (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Music in Schools Today [MUST] (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Science (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - National Information Infrastructure (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - National Institute of Standards and Technology (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - National Research Council (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - NCR Corporation (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Notebook computer conceptual sketches, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - OCT contest (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - OCT 1-800- service (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Office of Technology Assessment [1 of 4] (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Office of Technology Assessment [2 of 4] (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Office of Technology Assessment [3 of 4] (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Office of Technology Assessment [4 of 4] (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Palo Alto camps (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Palo Alto dance (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Palo Alto Design Group (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Palo Alto Schools (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - PARC [1 of 2] (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - PARC [2 of 2] (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - PARC Managing for Results: 1998 goals & annual objectives, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - PARC Study group [1 of 3], 1997 Oct. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - PARC Study group [2 of 3], 1997 Oct. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - PARC Study group [3 of 3], 1997 Oct. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - PARC survey results (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - PARC TAB stuff (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - PC Watch (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Personal Communications Devices (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Personal Communications Services (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Survey CSL (Mark Weiser) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Personnel transfer: Ed Richley (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Pesanelli, David (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Philips (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Philips Consumer Electronics: Philips Consumer Electronics Co., 1996 June 7 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Physical Science QIT [1 of 3], 1990 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Physical Science QIT [2 of 3], 1990 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Physical Science QIT [3 of 3], 1990 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - P.I. reports [1 of 7] (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - P.I. reports [2 of 7] (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - P.I. reports [3 of 7] (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - P.I. reports [4 of 7] (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - P.I. reports [5 of 7] (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - P.I. reports [6 of 7] (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - P.I. reports [7 of 7] (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Pierce (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Plans for space meeting (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Platform decommission (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Poland (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Portable X Windows (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee - Interim report to the President, 1998 Aug. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Press clippings - general (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Price Waterhouse: [Tacit proposal to serve at Independent Accountants], 1995 Oct. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Proctor & Gamble (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Product information from trade shows (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Project reviews [1 of 2] (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Project reviews [2 of 2] (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Publications (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Publication clearances & logs (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Purchase orders (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Pure Imaginations - Portland, Oregon, 1995 June 27 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Radio Mail (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Rank XEROX (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Receipts / copies (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Red Herring article (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Red Herring article: invited article for Red Herring due 1995 May 25 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Resumes (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Interesting resumes (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - RGB Technology (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Responsive environment (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Robots (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Roose, Debbie (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Russell, Dan [1 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Russell, Dan [2 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Russell, Daniel M. (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Saber-C (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Santa Clara University - proposal for a Master of Science in Software Engineering (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Schematics (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Schematics (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Alan Bell Schematics (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Steve Jackson Schematics (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - SCIAM II [1 of 3] (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - SCIAM II [2 of 3] (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - SCIAM II [3 of 3] (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - The Science-technology relation and industrial innovation (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Seattle Silicon: cheap radios (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Seattle Silicon: miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Security Infotral (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Senior staff off-site meeting, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Seybold, 1991 June (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Signal processing (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Silicon Graphics, Inc. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Silicon Graphics, Inc. agreement (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Silicon Valley Entrepreneur's Conference (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Silicon Valley meeting, 1998 Dec. 10 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Situated innovation: organizational learning and values issues. Proposal submitted to National Science Foundation, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Smart Visualization software (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Smithsonian Awards [1 of 2] (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Smithsonian Awards [2 of 2] (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Software Patent Institute [SPI]: agreement (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Software Reuse Committee (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Sony (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Sony barcode command sheet for LD (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - SRI International (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - SSL monthly reports (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Stanford University [1 of 3] (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Stanford University [2 of 3] (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University [3 of 3] (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Computer Forum [1 of 2], 1995 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Computer Forum [2 of 2], 1995 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University Computer Forum. Profiles of B.S. students, 1996 June (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University Computer Forum. Profiles of M.S. students, 1996 June (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University Computer Forum. Profiles of Ph.D. students, 1996 June (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University Continuing Education Program (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University CS 230 Prof. Smith. Custom course material, 1991 - 1992 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University CS 230 Prof. Smith. Custom course material, pt. 2, 1991 - 1992 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University: Stanford School of Business job listing form (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University: Stanford Telecom Center (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Stern marketing (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Strategy contract preparation [1 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Strategy contract preparation [2 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Strategy review, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Summer interns (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - SUN [1 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - SUN [2 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - SUN [1 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - SUN [2 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - SUN (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - SUN - 2.0 direction & news tech (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - SUN / David D. Lee (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - SUN product information (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - SUN User's Group [SUG] (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - SunDragon [1 of 4], 1989 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - SunDragon [2 of 4], 1989 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - SunDragon [3 of 4], 1989 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - SunDragon [4 of 4], 1989 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - SunDragon, 1991 - 1992 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - SunProgrammer (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - SUN/Xerox Shared audio software, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Supplies, 1988 Feb. - Mar. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Support staff promotions (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Systems portfolio (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - TabTeam meeting (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Tacit, Inc. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Tacit comp. & documentation (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Tacit dimensions (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - People in Tacit - entered in database (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Fuji - Xerox / Tacit (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Tacit - Satchels - FX (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Tacit - distributors (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Tacit - presentation, 1996 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Tacit - Lance Becker (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - TadPole (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Tanner Research (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - TDMB (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Tech Museum of Innovation (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Technological infrastructure (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Thermometer (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 3-D Image Tech (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 3M (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Timex (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Trademark (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Trip reports: Consumer electronics show, Las Vegas, 1994 Jan. 7 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Trojan horses, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Tuulari, Esa (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - TWOWS (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Ubiquitous [1 of 2] (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Ubiquitous [2 of 2] (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Ubi Computing Patent Advisory Committee (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Ubiquitous Computing patents (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Ubiquitous Computing workshop, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Ubiquitous Computing workshop. Additional position papers, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - UCO Board of Advisors (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - UCO Key chain 1 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - UCO: UCO Board of Advisors meeting (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - UCO: Harvard Buiz school [1 of 2] (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - UCO: Harvard Buiz school [2 of 2] (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - University of California (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - University of California - Microelectronics innovation and computer research opportunities (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - University of California at Berkeley [1 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - University of California at Berkeley [2 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - University of California at Berkeley [3 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - University of California at Berkeley [4 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - University of California at Davis [1 of 5] (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - University of California at Davis [2 of 5] (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - University of California at Davis [3 of 5] (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - University of California at Davis [4 of 5] (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - University of California at Davis [5 of 5] (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - University of California, San Diego. Dept. of Computer Science and Engineering Graduate Program Review [1 of 4], 1998 - 1999 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - University of California, San Diego. Dept. of Computer Science and Engineering Graduate Program Review [2 of 4], 1998 - 1999 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - University of California, San Diego. Dept. of Computer Science and Engineering Graduate Program Review [3 of 4], 1998 - 1999 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - University of California, San Diego. Dept. of Computer Science and Engineering Graduate Program Review [4 of 4], 1998 - 1999 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - University of California, San Diego (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - University of Michigan - IPOCSE (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - University of Washington (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - University of Washington / PARC proposal for subcontract, 1999 Jan. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Update: a weekly publication of the Information Center at PARC (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Upset Technologies (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Robotics vs. Palm Computing (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Usage rights (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Venture capital firms (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Venture capital - rejection letters (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Venture capitalists (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Venture capital - general (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Visible spectrum, monolithic, multi-wavelength laser diode array: a proposal / submitted by a Spectra Diode Labs - Xerox Team (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Misc. vitaes (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Want, Roy (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Webster Research Center Printing (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Weiser, Mark - performance appraisal (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Weyerhauser (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Who's who in the world (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - WINLAB [1 of 2] (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - WINLAB [2 of 2] (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Wireless Communications Alliance (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Wireless communications in smart handheld devices, 1996 Dec. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - WQED Committee (The Next Age) (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - WRC monthly reports (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - WRL research report [1 of 4], 1988 Feb. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - WRL research report [2 of 4], 1988 Feb. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - WRL research report [3 of 4], 1988 Feb. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - WRL research report [4 of 4], 1988 Feb. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Xerox, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Xerox [1 of 3], 1997 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Xerox [2 of 3], 1997 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Xerox [3 of 3], 1997 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Xerox 1998 direction, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Xerox 2000 [1 of 2], 1999 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Xerox 2000 [2 of 2], 1999 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Xerox 2000 assumptions, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Xerox - Annual University Grant Award meeting, 1986 Nov. 9-11 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Xerox articles (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Xerox - Board of Directors (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Xerox - Corporate Innovation Council (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Xerox Executive Workshop, Webster, New York, 1994 Jan. 20 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Xerox history [1 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Xerox history [2 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Xerox history [3 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Xerox information [1 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Xerox information [2 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Xerox internal information - miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Xerox Internet background [1 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Xerox Internet background [2 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Xerox Internet background [3 of 3] (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Xerox, Internet, web [1 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Xerox, Internet, web [2 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Xerox invention proposal / David L. Hecht (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Xerox - miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Xerox PARC (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Xerox PARC occupancy blueprint (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Xerox policy (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Xerox preliminary audit: version, 1999 Feb. 15 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Xerox reading changes, 1998 Dec. 17 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Xerox technology strategy '96, 1996 Oct. 1 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Xerox, The Document Company (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Xerox - TDMB (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Xerox: Xerox policy letter no. 2 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - XIWT (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - XIWT (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - XIWT [1 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - XIWT [2 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - XNS support on SUN workstations (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - XSoft (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Young, David and Julius van der Wat (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Young, David and Julius van der Wat. Scrapbook [1 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Young, David and Julius van der Wat. Scrapbook [2 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Zendex (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - ZMob projects, University of Maryland (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Series 6. Notebooks
  - Notepad, [1976 - 1977] (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Memo book, 1977 Mar. 3 - 1977 Oct. 16 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Computation book, 1987 Aug. 10 - 1994 Oct. 7 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Computation book, 1991 Jan. 10 - 1994 June 29 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, 1995 Apr. 24 - 1997 Mar. 19 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Notepad, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Notepad, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Notepad, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous notes, ca. 1999 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Note on chat with Clinton on the Internet, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Clinton, William Jefferson.
  - Notebook, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Notes, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Moving trip, ca. 1985 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Note cards, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Series 7. Talks
  This extensive series consists primarily of the transparencies and lecture notes used by Mark Weiser in his talks around the world.
  - Mark Weiser publication clearances [1 of 4], 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Mark Weiser publication clearances [2 of 4], 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Mark Weiser publication clearances [3 of 4], 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Mark Weiser publication clearances [4 of 4], 1994-1997 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Mark Weiser publication clearances, 1998-[1999] (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Incremental re-execution [1 of 2], 1987 June 21 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Incremental re-execution [2 of 2], 1987 June 21 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Portable Cedar dealer, 1987 Oct. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Cedar ports plan, 1987 Nov. 17 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Haddon talk (runtime), 1987 Nov. 24 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - IGC Dealer, 1987 Nov. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Runtime dealer, 1987 Dec. 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - System 33 measuring, 1987 Dec. 18 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Welcome to PARC, ca. 1987 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - System 33 so far!!, 1988 Feb. 4 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - System 33 Board meeting, 1988 Feb. 24 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - A slow file system, 1988 Mar. 3 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - System 33 for Spencer, 1988 Mar. 3 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Runtime, 1988 Mar. 21 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Situated programming, 1988 May 9 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Open systems, 1988 June 2 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Spencer-integration overview, 1988 June 8 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Forum talk: Seams and cloth: the future of computer science research, 1988 Nov. 8 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Penzias, Bell Labs "The future of computing", 1988 Nov. 10 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Slow file system, 1988 Dec. 7 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - System 33 Berkeley, 1988 Dec. 7 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - CSL and me, 1988 Dec. 13 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - WRC talk about PCR & CSL, 1989 Jan. 16 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Portable common runtime at Apple Computer, 1989 Jan. 16 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Beyond workstations, 1989 Feb. 13 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Al Perlis Dealer transparencies, 1989 May 3 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - MIT Club, 1989 May 15 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Portable common runtime (PCR) at SUN, 1989 May 23 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Interns talk (UBICOMP), 1989 June 23 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Ubiquitous Computing, 1989 June 23 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - E.R. Squibb, 1989 June 26 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - SunDragon presentation to EML, 1989 Oct. 11 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Cedar for Andrews, 1989 Oct. 30 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 1990 CSL plan, 1989 Nov. 3 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Portable common runtime (PCR), 1989 Dec. 1 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - SOSP PCR transparencies - Ubi Comp, 1989 Dec. 1 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - SOSP "outrageous" proposal, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - El Segundo Ed Badlan & Ubi Comp briefing, 1990 Jan. 24 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - ED presentation (Dragon, Badlan), 1990 May (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - De Anza College, 1990 Nov. 14 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - CSL OP Plan presentation, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - SUN/PARC cooperative projects, 1991 Jan. 7 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Software prototyping, 1991 Feb. 10 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Globalview futures for AMEX, 1991 Apr. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - DARPA Ubi talk, 1991 Aug. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - DARPA/Ubi talk [John R. White 1991 Nov. 25], 1991 Aug. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - XSoft Ubiquitous Computing, 1991 Nov. 6 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - XSoft/CRL meeting, 1991 Nov. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Technological partners: the personal computer outlook panel discussion, 1991 Dec. 9-10 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - University of Michigan/Berkeley, 1992 Feb. 1 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Circus talk, 1992 Mar. 10 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - University of Michigan wireless data net "UMichTalk", 1992 Apr. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Career development, 1992 June (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - DARPA, 1992 June & Aug. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Ubiquitous Computing, 1992 Sept. 29 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - MIT agents, 1992 Oct. 6 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Agents/MIT, 1992 Oct. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - NSF libraries, 1992 Dec. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Andersen University of Michigan, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Andersen University of Michigan [transparencies], 1992 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Andersen University of Michigan [print-out], 1992 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - CR&T survey, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - XIWT, 1993 Jan. 7 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - [The Chameleon] Spatially aware palmtops [George Fitzmaurice], 1993 Jan. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Motorola, 1993 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - University of Washington: System and Architecture Challenges, Symposium "ArchSymposium", 1993 Apr. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - UBICOMP workshop at PARC, 1993 Apr. 5 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - SIM presentation, Palm Springs, Calif., 1993 Apr. 16 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Toronto talk, 1993 Apr. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Boeing presentation, 1993 May 14; 1993 July 14 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Telecom Conference "Stanford Telecom", 1993 May 18 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - International Software Engineering Conference "JSCS slicing", 1993 May 21 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - CR&T kick-off meeting "Changeology", 1993 June 11 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Changeology given to the CR&T staff, 1993 June 15 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - PARC Senior Staff "On hiring outstanding people", 1993 July 16 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Systems Portfolio Experts Team "CSL overview" PARC, 1993 July 27 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Systems Portfolio Experts Team "CSL overview" PARC to SPFEL talk, 1993 July 27; 1993 Aug. 17 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Snowbird conference, 1993 July (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Experiences with X in a wireless environment, 1993 Aug. 3 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Some research issues in Ubiquitous Computing given by A. Demers - ACM/PODC, 1993 Aug. 18 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Ubiquitous computing & implication for telecommunications - PARC to Gensler & Associates, The Wireless Communication Alliance, Sunnyvale, Calif., 1993 Aug. 31 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - The Wireless Communication Alliance (presentation) ESL building M-5, Sunnyvale, Calif., 1993 Aug. 31 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - How CSL is broken (Dealer), 1993 Sept. 22 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Ubiquitous Computing, 1993 Oct. 28 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Ubi-Talk slides. -- 40 transparencies, 1993 Oct. 28 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Technology transfer, 1993 Nov. 9 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Selected Ubi-talk transparencies [1 of 2], 1993 Nov. 16 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Selected Ubi-talk transparencies [2 of 2], 1993 Nov. 16 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - ARPA Wireless & Low Power conference, Palo Alto, 1994 Jan. 11 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - IRIF talk, 1994 Jan. 31 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - EIL viewed from CSL talk, 1994 Feb. 8 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - CSL budget for 1994 Dealer, 1994 Feb. 16 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - XSoft Technology Interchange Ubicomp talk, 1994 Feb. 21 (Box 66, Folder 3)